How do you create your own step, pretty much all the time comes from your heart.
Comes a little bit more how you feel the music.
Yeah.
It's very simple how to create your step if you feel the music.
So, every time you want to create your own step, just put the music, listen to the music, just put out a little bit loud, if you're driving, even if you're home, you can put the music, you can start doing some homework all around the house, you can do everything pretty much that you love to do like put some music on it.
Like for example, fixing your car or be outside your house or be inside your house, whatever, you all the time, for creating your own step, you're going to need your music.
Yes.
Put the music, feel it, and like I said before, if you feel, if it feels good, it's going to look good.
Don't worry about it. Okay. So all the time, try to use your body as a tool and however you feel the music, for me, it has to be fast.
When the music goes a little bit fast, and when the music kicks a little bit higher, and this is when I like to create my own step.
So I like everything just pretty much fast and move, and pretty much have me excited with that the extra beat of music they have.
So don't worry about it, if you need to create your own step, the only thing you need to do is turn up the music, put some music and just let it go.
Okay.
See you in the next step.